[Music]
[音乐]
welcome everyone thanks for attending my
欢迎大家感谢您参加我的
talk about Java modules at breakfast
在早餐时谈论Java模块
with spring food but first let me
春季食物，但首先让我
introduce myself my name is jab comas
自我介绍，我叫贾布·科马斯
I'm a Java developer I work for a group
我是Java开发人员，在一个小组工作
9:00 in the Netherlands and that's also
9:00在荷兰，那也是
very live in in Tilburg city in the
非常住在提尔堡市
south of the Netherlands and I've been
在荷兰南部，我去过
doing job ever since 2002 professionally
自2002年以来从事专业工作
since 2006 and outside work I'm also
自2006年以来，我还从事外部工作
father and a husband and I like to play
父亲和丈夫，我喜欢玩
board games not just holding them pretty
棋盘游戏不仅使它们漂亮
leaf or a picture but actually playing
叶或图片，但实际上在播放
them so enough about me
他们对我如此了解
you're here for the modules so what's
你在这里的模块，所以
the current state of the module system
模块系统的当前状态
they've been introduced in September of
他们是在9月推出的
2017 so it's been roughly a year and a
2017年大约已经一年零了
half
半
so where are we at first of all dueling
所以我们首先在哪里决斗
sport pretty good I even was ready from
运动很好，我什至已经准备好了
the get-go
一开始
most i des have support for modules
我大多数人都支持模块
there's even some rumors that you can
甚至有传言说你可以
work with modules with Gradle I'm not a
与Gradle一起使用模块我不是
great little user I know it's not
伟大的小用户，我知道这不是
officially supported but apparently it
官方支持，但显然是
works pretty well
效果很好
so from that perspective we're good we
所以从这个角度来看我们很好
can use them we can work with them but
可以使用它们，我们可以与他们合作，但是
we also use a lot of frameworks and
我们还使用了很多框架
libraries obviously and the adoption of
图书馆显然是通过
modules amongst them is actually pretty
其中的模块实际上很漂亮
low still and that also has to do of
仍然很低，这也与
course that they in turn depend on
他们反过来依赖的课程
orders and they're waiting for each
订单，他们正在等待每个
other and there's other concerns but
其他还有其他问题
still not really a lot of adoption there
那里还没有被很多人采用
and an even worse developers like you
还有像你这样的更糟糕的开发者
and me the adoption among them is really
而我当中的领养人真的
really low I did a project with modules
非常低，我做了一个带有模块的项目
a couple of months ago and I've spoken
几个月前，我讲过
to many people about them ever since it
从那以后对许多人
was no single auto developer outside
外面没有一个汽车开发商
their project visit yeah I work with
他们的项目访问是的，我与
so there's still a way to go but what's
所以还有一段路要走，但是
holding us back then why aren't we all
那么阻碍我们前进，为什么我们都没有
using windows because we've been begging
使用Windows，因为我们一直在乞求
for it or some of us have been craving
因为它或我们中有些人渴望
for it ever since it was announced for
自从它宣布为
Java 7 initially and actually there's a
最初是Java 7，实际上有一个
talk of some of Mark I attended last
我最后参加的一些马克的谈话
year and he said yeah well most people
那年，他说是的，大多数人都很好
perceive perceived as eating the veggies
感觉被认为是在吃蔬菜
you know it's healthy but there's
你知道它很健康，但是有
something about them and yet these are
关于他们的东西，但这些是
my kids and you could tell by the faces
我的孩子，你可以从脸上看出
something is not right something it's
有些不对的东西
not right and I agree with them because
不对，我同意他们的看法，因为
we we love our veggies so more modules
我们爱我们的蔬菜，所以有更多的模块
more veggies okay you like it
更多蔬菜好吧，你喜欢它
I see the doubt in your faces why why do
我看到你的脸上有疑问，为什么要做
you like modules and for that I want to
您喜欢模块，为此，我想
take you back a little bit in time and
带您回到过去
tell a little story because last year I
讲一个小故事，因为去年我
started at a client of mine he had a big
从我的一个客户开始，他有一个很大的
legacy application and that has been in
旧版应用程序已经存在
development for roughly 15 years
发展约15年
hundreds of developers working on that a
数百名从事此工作的开发人员
lot of legacy even legacy within the
许多遗产，甚至是
legacy and there was a little bit of an
遗产，有一点
architecture picture resembling the
建筑图片类似于
thing you see on screen right now it's
您现在在屏幕上看到的东西是
not exactly that of course but they
当然不完全是，但是他们
nicely isolated their legacy system
很好地隔离了他们的遗留系统
their legacy framework that was built
他们建立的旧框架
in-house and then build up a new
在内部，然后建立一个新的
architecture of size that will was
大小的架构将是
layered not my favorite type of
分层不是我最喜欢的类型
architecture but there was some
建筑，但有一些
structure but
结构但是
after a couple of hours I realized this
几个小时后，我意识到了这一点
was more accurate so more modules more
更精确，所以更多模块
dependencies especially dependencies
依赖关系，尤其是依赖关系
pointing in all kinds of directions that
指向各种方向
were never intended to be there but this
从来没有打算在那里
was traceable it was all in the pom
可以追溯到一切都在绒球中
files so okay fair enough and you could
文件足够合理，您可以
not expect that from a system that's
不要指望从
been 15 years in the making
已经有15年的历史了
continuously but then I continued and
不断，但后来我继续
after a couple of weeks I realized this
几周后，我意识到了这一点
wasn't even a full picture it was just a
甚至还不完整
picture of the structure of the sources
来源结构图
the runtime dependencies were even more
运行时依赖性甚至更多
there were actually calls via reflection
实际上有通过反思的电话
from the lowest level resistance layer
从最低级别的电阻层开始
to the surface layers so a lot of
到表面层那么多
circular dependencies it was a mess and
循环依赖是一团糟，
this was actually the first portrait
这实际上是第一张肖像
project I was ever in where I stopped
我曾经去过的项目
refactoring a little piece after week
一周后重构一小块
because it was just plain impossible it
因为那简直是不可能的
was really a spaghetti so when we got
真的是意大利面，所以当我们得到
the chance there with our team to start
我们的团队有机会开始
on a new application I thought okay
在一个新的应用程序上，我认为还可以
apparently there's some difficulty here
显然这里有些困难
with maintaining our architecture let's
保持我们的架构，让我们
see if modules can help us out
看看模块是否可以帮助我们
so what we started out with was a
所以我们开始的是
proof-of-concept application and another
概念验证应用程序和另一个
team already built
团队已经建立
Springwood Java 8 so which was already
Springwood Java 8所以已经
better than what we had but I wanted to
比我们拥有的要好，但我想
prevent further problems so what I will
防止进一步的问题，所以我会
be showing you today is demo that's more
今天向您展示的是演示，更多
or less similar of what I did for that
或与我所做的不太相似
client but before we go there what
客户，但在我们去那里之前
challenges will we face there's actually
我们将面对的挑战实际上是
two major challenges right now if you
如果您现在面临两个主要挑战
want to migrate your applications to two
想要将您的应用程序迁移到两个
modules first of all split packages a
模块首先是拆分包
split package is a package with the same
拆分包装是具有相同包装的包装
name that's being exported by more than
被超过
one module or your module file the
一个模块或您的模块文件
module system doesn't allow it and now
模块系统现在不允许
you might think okay that's not too big
您可能会认为还不错
of an issue we we don't have that just
我们没有这个问题
imagine
想像
larger frameworks larger libraries that
更大的框架更大的库
are spread across multiple jars mostly
大部分散布在多个罐子中
they share the same route back each
他们共享相同的路线
night and sometimes in that route
晚上，有时在那条路
package there's classes in different
打包有不同的类
jars it's your first flick the split
罐子，这是你第一次甩开
package already so it's really out there
包装已经存在，所以它真的在那里
second problem or not a problem by
第二个问题或不是一个问题
themselves are automatic modules
本身是自动模块
automatic module is module that is not
自动模块是不是
actually module just plain jar file but
实际上模块只是普通的jar文件，但是
it's on your module pop so it's
它在您的模块弹出窗口上，所以
interpreted as a module by the JVM and
由JVM解释为模块，并且
it has a couple of properties for
它具有几个特性
instance an automatic module by default
默认情况下实例一个自动模块
exports and opens all inspectors to the
出口并向所有检查员开放
outside world and also it reads all all
外部世界，它也读取所有
the modules and up until here does not
模块，直到这里没有
too big of a problem it's just the
问题太大，只是
behavior you already had on JDK 8 all
您已经在JDK 8 all上拥有的行为
over this is how these jars were
这些罐子是这样的
supposed to be used okay but the next
应该可以用，但是下一个
point is a little bit of an issue
一点是一个问题
because the name of an automatic module
因为自动模块的名称
is derived from the file name so version
是从文件名派生的，因此版本
identifiers are stripped of special
标识符被去除特殊
characters are stripped off and then
字符被剥离，然后
you're left with module name that's
您剩下的模块名称是
that's derived from the actual farm line
从实际的农场线衍生而来
of the artifact and again you might
的神器，你可能会再次
think okay not too big of an issue it's
认为没什么大不了的
okay but you can't have more than one
好的，但是你不能超过一个
module on your module path with the same
与模块路径上的模块相同
name and what was called from the Apache
名称和Apache的名称
maven foundation actually did some
Maven基金会实际上做了一些
research and he found 3,500 possible
研究，他发现3,500种可能
collisions in maven channel 11 so that's
在Maven频道11中发生碰撞
outside your own internal libraries and
在您自己的内部库之外
some of these aren't that harmful like
其中一些不是那么有害
the artifact ID parent it's not
工件ID父级不是
something you will depend on as a
你会依赖的东西
library but a runner-up actually is the
图书馆，但实际上是亚军
artifact ID the library which is
工件ID库是
something you will depend on as a
你会依赖的东西
library so there's a possible issue
库，所以可能有问题
luckily there's
幸运的是
a word rant or a way to prevent that for
一词或防止这种情况的方法
library maintainer and they can add an
库维护者，他们可以添加一个
automatic module name entry in a
自动模块名称输入
manifest file and it's a way of saying
清单文件，这是一种表达方式
okay if I will ever become a module this
好吧，如果我能成为这个模块
will be my name so that way you can
将是我的名字，这样你就可以
define a unique module name and by now
定义一个唯一的模块名称，到现在
most of the community have settled on
大多数社区都定居下来
reverse DNS naming for that like we do
像我们一样反向DNS命名
with our packages like we do with our
与我们的包裹一样
maven group IDs that really results in
真正产生的Maven组ID
their unique module names okay now if
它们的唯一模块名称现在可以了
off the theory what will we be building
从理论上讲，我们将要建立什么
so like a set and I board games so I
就像一个场景，我下棋，所以我
thought okay my denim can be about board
我以为我的牛仔布可以和董事会有关
games I've built a really simple
我构建的游戏非常简单
application that allows you to post and
允许您发布和
get some information about board games
获取有关棋盘游戏的一些信息
and also of course it's nice to know
当然也很高兴知道
some writings is it worth playing
一些著作值得一玩
so my architecture will look something
所以我的架构看起来会有些变化
like this at a very about them there's a
像这样，关于他们，有一个
domain module has no dependencies
域模块没有依赖性
whatsoever pure Java then on top of that
任何纯Java然后最重要的是
there is the modules that form the
有形成
boundary of the system so there's a
系统的边界，所以有一个
resistance layer with spring data Mongo
带有Spring 数据Mongo的阻力层
and there's a rest api depending on
还有一个休息api
spring web and then you see a module
Spring Web，然后您看到一个模块
BoardGameGeek client for those of you
适用于您的BoardGameGeek客户端
not aware BoardGameGeek is the biggest
不知道BoardGameGeek是最大的
website in world about board games has
关于棋盘游戏世界的网站有
information about any board game you can
有关您可以玩的任何棋盘游戏的信息
imagine and the nice thing is they
想像和高兴的是他们
expose an XML API via which I can get
公开我可以通过的XML API
their writings board games because I
他们的棋盘游戏，因为我
have so little users that's better to to
用户很少，最好去
get the writing somewhere else and also
把书写到别的地方
it gives a nice demo effect so for a DEP
它提供了很好的演示效果，因此对于DEP
module on depending on Jacobi and I'm
模块取决于雅可比和我
using open frame there's a rest client
使用开放式框架有一个休息的客户
and then of course I want my
然后我当然想要我的
applications to be secure so there's a
应用程序是安全的，所以有一个
security module with spring security
具有Spring 安全性的安全模块
using some web though JSON web token
通过JSON Web令牌使用某些Web
library and to pull it all together
图书馆并将其整合在一起
that's the application module and that
那是应用程序模块
actually depends
实际取决于
spring boot okay that was a little lie
spring boot 好吧，那是一个小谎言
on that slide sorry for that
在那张幻灯片上，对此感到抱歉
so the actual project I did was with db2
所以我做的实际项目是db2
and I thought well wouldn't it be more
我想这会不会更多
sexy for my demo if I use manga and
如果我使用漫画和
unfortunately I already had an issue
不幸的是我已经遇到了问题
there so apparently there's a split
所以显然有一个分裂
package issue and the legacy MongoDB
软件包问题和旧版MongoDB
clients and at first I thought okay I'll
客户，起初我以为我会
work around that there's a newer monger
解决附近有一个新的商人
to be client the async one and that has
成为异步客户端，并且
no split package issue they specifically
他们没有专门的拆包问题
resolved that so I will be good but then
解决了，所以我会很好，但是
it turns out that spring data Mongo
事实证明， spring data Mongo
actually relies pretty heavily on the
实际上非常依赖
legacy MongoDB client so what's stuck
旧版MongoDB客户程序
there so sorry for that I went back to
在那里很抱歉，我回到了
spring data JPA and it's now running
Spring数据JPA，它正在运行
with a post course database so how do we
与课程后数据库，那么我们如何
go about that the first thing you want
去做你想要的第一件事
to do when you want to migrate your
想要迁移您的主机时要做的
application to modules is to get your
应用到模块是为了让您
dependencies up-to-date and of course
当然是最新的依赖项
there's many other reasons to do that
还有很多其他原因
like security support features that you
例如您的安全支持功能
need but in this case as I said there's
需要，但正如我所说，在这种情况下
not many libraries that really adopted
真正采用的图书馆不多
it yet but it's an ongoing process more
还没有，但这是一个持续的过程
and more well at to the field and by
而且更擅长领域
upgrading to the latest dependencies you
升级到您最新的依赖项
just eliminate some possible problems
消除一些可能的问题
that you will run into with older
你会遇到老
versions so it's a matter of creating a
版本，因此只需创建一个
smaller space for your problem in your
在您的问题中占用较小的空间
face or challenge so step 2
面对或挑战，所以第2步
same reason run your application with
同样的原因运行您的应用程序
JDK 11 or higher if you and don't
如果您不愿意，请使用JDK 11或更高版本
already do so because there are some
已经这样做了，因为有一些
tricky stuff in there like for this
像这样的棘手的东西
application I'm depending on Jax P which
应用程序取决于Jax P
has been removed from Java 11 so I first
已从Java 11中删除，所以我先
had to replace it with some other
必须用其他替代它
objective here
目标在这里
so I chose the the RI of exp next step
所以我选择了下一步的RI
further in line go file with jdk 11 or
使用jdk 11进一步进入go文件或
higher again this is just to make the
再高一点，这只是为了使
problem space smaller so actually these
问题空间较小，所以实际上这些
steps are just preparation let's look
步骤只是准备，让我们来看看
for prepare the module structure so in
用于准备模块结构
my case the application that we
我的情况下，我们的申请
inherited was actually one big single
继承的实际上是一个大单
maven module so it was nicely structured
Maven模块，所以结构很好
that was okay but on the source level it
没关系，但是从源代码上看
was still warm module and what I did
还是温暖的模块，我做了什么
there was first grading a big job of
首先是对
modular out of that application and then
模块化的应用程序，然后
later split it up and I wouldn't do that
后来把它分开，我不会那样做
again because it got me right into all
再次因为它使我正确
the details and all the issues to run
详细信息和所有要运行的问题
into that you can possibly see because
您可能会看到，因为
everything will work out in one code and
一切都将在一个代码中完成，
by splitting up in your module structure
通过拆分您的模块结构
before you're actually migrating to Java
在实际迁移到Java之前
modules you can go module by module step
您可以逐个模块地学习模块
by step and therefore also making your
一步一步，因此也使您的
problem space smaller going over
问题空间较小
iterations so then step 5 logically is
迭代，因此从逻辑上讲，第5步是
add module descriptors butterman so you
添加模块描述符butterman，以便您
start with the module at the very bottom
从最底部的模块开始
of your dependency graph because it has
您的依赖关系图，因为它具有
no dependencies or a little amount of
没有依赖性或少量
dependencies and so here we will
依赖关系，所以在这里我们将
actually see some code so let's switch
实际看到一些代码，所以让我们切换
over to my IDE
转到我的IDE
and as you see I have a application here
如您所见，我在这里有一个应用程序
I did all the preparation of the steps I
我已经做好了所有步骤的准备工作
described before and there's an
之前描述过，有一个
application model module for what Gamgee
Gamgee的应用程序模型模块
clients the domain module persisters
客户端域模块持久性
module REST API security it's all there
模块REST API安全性
and to show what it does let's start it
并展示它的作用，让我们开始吧
okay it's up so first of all I need to
好吧，所以我首先需要
login and that gets me JSON web token
登录并获得JSON Web令牌
postman will pick that up and apply it
邮递员将把它捡起来并套用
to the next command I want to create a
到我要创建的下一个命令
board game so this is a post endpoint
棋盘游戏，所以这是发布终点
sending the board game it's created and
发送创建的棋盘游戏，
it returns a result giving me back an ID
它返回结果给我一个ID
again postman will pick that up so I can
邮递员会再接一次，所以我可以
check can I retrieve the game yes I can
检查我可以找回游戏吗，可以
and as you see here there's also
如您所见，这里还有
BoardGameGeek ID so that's the
BoardGameGeek ID，所以
identifier that's a board game he uses
他使用的棋盘游戏标识符
so I have a separate time points to get
所以我有一个单独的时间点
the writings from work and week let's
工作和周的著作让我们
see if that works it does so it's well
看看是否行得通，所以很好
seven-point night for this game if you
如果您有这个游戏的七点夜晚
don't believe it
不相信
let's see it's this game on board game
让我们看看这是棋盘游戏
geek okay they also say seven point
怪胎好吧，他们也说了七点
eight so it's actually working cool but
八个所以它实际上工作很酷，但是
now of course we're here for the
现在我们当然在这里
migration so starting off at the very
迁移，所以从最开始
bottom of the module graph you see
您看到的模块图的底部
intelligent support it says okay crank
智能支持它说好吧曲柄
me on module in football and there we go
我参加足球课程，然后去
so reverse dns name
所以反向DNS名称
this way my module name is unique and
这样我的模块名称是唯一的，
this is module without any dependencies
这是没有任何依赖性的模块
so I didn't have to declare any requires
所以我不必声明任何要求
here and I can just say okay there's two
在这里，我可以说有两个
packages in there the root level package
根目录级别的软件包
and a command package and these are
和命令包，这些是
relevant to the rest of my application
与我的其余申请相关
so I want export this
所以我要导出这个
okay that's it my first module
好的，这就是我的第一个模块
description it's done okay so now let's
描述它已经完成了，所以现在让我们
check if we can get that to pop up so
检查我们是否可以弹出它，以便
now using maven directly let's see what
现在直接使用Maven让我们看看
it does okay
没关系
it's running oh I just started and
它正在运行，哦，我才刚开始
already have an error so as you see here
已经有一个错误，如您所见
it's complaining about some fork issues
抱怨一些叉子问题
and has to do with my unit tests
与我的单元测试有关
so that's unit tests in there on using J
所以这是使用J进行的单元测试
unit Jupiter an apparently doesn't back
木星单位显然不会回来
and the Surefire plugin in relation with
和Surefire插件有关
modules and get you an interpreter so
模块并为您提供翻译
although I'm actually on the latest
虽然我实际上是最新的
final version of the Surefire plugin I
Surefire插件的最终版本I
will now upgrade it to a milestone
现在将其升级到一个里程碑
release which fixes the bug you could
释放可以修复的错误的版本
also set the four count to zero but
也将四个计数设置为零，但
that's just the workaround so let me fix
那只是解决方法，让我修复
that
那
okay there we go so it's a yes import
好吧，我们去吧，这是一个重要的
changes please it's a newer version so
更改，请使用较新的版本
let's see what it does now well it
让我们看看它现在做得如何
compile and run the tests
编译并运行测试
okay all the way till yeah
好吧，一直到
so cool no
太酷了
also check okay is it running sorry
还检查好吗，运行对不起
also check if it still runs and that's
还检查它是否仍然运行，那是
what I wanted to do so booting yes it's
我想做的是启动是的
up okay so let's briefly go through it
起来好吧，让我们简要地经历一下
see if it all works yes that works that
看看是否一切正常，是可行的
works okay fine
可以正常工作
so that was step one but this was the
这是第一步，但这是
easiest one so we'll now head on to the
最简单的一种，所以我们现在开始
next module and it's a little more
下一个模块，还有更多
complicated one security so it has no
复杂的一种证券因此没有
internal dependencies but it has
内部依赖关系，但它具有
external dependencies so I actually
外部依赖，所以我实际上
prepared this a little bit because
准备这一点，因为
otherwise it would become little tedious
否则它会变得乏味
so as you see it has quite a lot of
如您所见，它有很多
dependencies on several spring modules
对几个spring模块的依赖
and as you're gonna state it this
正如您要说的那样
morning
早上
spring is module yeah and it's not on
春天是模块，是的，它不在
the short-term roadmap but what they did
短期路线图，但他们做了什么
is defined automatic module names and
定义了自动模块名称，并且
all their jars so that's really cool
他们所有的罐子，这真的很酷
it helps me out as a developer using
它可以帮助我成为开发人员
modules and it doesn't force them into
模块，它不会强迫他们进入
be the common module of themselves so
成为自己的共同模块
that's good and that's why I separated
那很好，所以我分开了
these two out because these are actually
这两个是因为它们实际上是
derived from the file name and by
从文件名派生并由
separating them out in my virtual
将它们隔离在我的虚拟机中
descriptor I know okay this part is the
描述符，我知道这部分是
dangerous part if this ever becomes a
如果这成为一个危险的部分
module it might change nine and I might
模块可能会改变九，我可能
be hurt and then there's two packages in
被伤害，然后有两个包
there that I both need to export for
那里我都需要出口
spring okay good so that's working oh
春天还可以，所以可以了哦
sorry let's head on to the next one so
对不起，让我们继续下一个吧
this is the first one that actually has
这是第一个真正拥有的
an internal dependency the BoardGameGeek
内部依赖的BoardGameGeek
clients
客户
okay I was a little too quick with that
好吧，我有点太快了
okay
好的
so define a unique name again and here
所以在这里再定义一个唯一的名字
it depends on my domain module so it's
这取决于我的域模块，所以
nothing really fancy about that also
也没什么好看的
depends on exp and again Thane hasn't
取决于经验，再次塔恩没有
declared automatic module name so it
声明了自动模块名称，因此
separated them out then it exports only
分离出来然后只出口
one package but there's more in it so
一包，但里面还有更多
there's the root level package that has
有根级别的软件包
some implementations and an internal
一些实现和内部
interface
接口
there's the XML API package that's for
有用于的XML API包
the Jacobi and implementation but I only
Jacobi和实现，但我只
export the factory package because
出口工厂包装是因为
that's the only thing that really
那是唯一真正的
matters to do the rest of my application
要做我其余的应用程序很重要
it's the only thing I really want expose
这是我唯一想暴露的东西
the factory you will be used by spring
春天将要使用的工厂
to create create some beans for me but
为我创造一些beans，但是
it also opens the package and open says
它也打开包装，打开说
ok I want to make this available for
好的，我想将其提供给
deep reflection two orders and the
深层反思两个命令和
reason I did that here is because Jax
我这样做的原因是因为Jax
beef requires that it does deep
牛肉需要深
reflection on your cloths so ok got that
反射在你的衣服上，好了
working let's see if it still runs mmm
工作，让我们看看它是否仍在运行
that was quick ok so there's a much of
很快就可以了，所以有很多
missing we'll see about that later and
思念我们稍后会看到
there's a lot of these here ok reach
这里有很多这些可以到达
package come son external bind from both
包来自两者的外部绑定
jacobi in pool inject be cool okay so
雅各比在游泳池注入凉爽好吧，所以
that is a split package issue so in the
这是一个拆分包问题，因此在
currents latest version of checks be 2.3
当前最新版本的支票是2.3
they're split split package issue and I
他们是拆分包问题，我
was really struggling ok how do we get
真的很挣扎，我们如何获得
around this one and luckily in maven
幸运的是在这个附近
central there's also kind of a yeah it's
中央还有一种是的
it's a built version of 2.4 but yeah
这是2.4的内置版本，但是
there's some issues with a Java EE
Java EE存在一些问题
moving forward currently so but it's
目前正在前进，但这是
already on May 4 central so you can
已经在5月4日中央，所以您可以
perfectly use it so let's fix that so
完美使用它，让我们修复一下
there's a couple of dependencies in here
这里有几个依赖项
including the one it was complaining
包括它抱怨的那个
about that it couldn't find and I can
关于它找不到，我可以
replace these all with one
用一个替换所有这些
so you see includes built numer which
所以你看到包括内置的数字
says ok this is not really a final
说好吧，这不是最终决定
version but it works for me in this case
版本，但在这种情况下对我有用
I'm not saying that you should do this
我并不是说你应该这样做
directly in production in any
直接在任何生产中
application but it's worth considering
应用程序，但值得考虑
so that should do the trick
这样就可以了
okay it's now booting and it's there
好吧，现在正在启动，并且在那里
okay cool
好酷
so we're some way already now let's do
现在我们已经有了某种方式
the final two resistance and a module
最后两个电阻和一个模块
descriptor there again has an unique
描述符那里又有一个独特的
module name at the top depends on my
顶部的模块名称取决于我
domain module depends on java
域模块取决于Java
persistence defense on spring data api
Spring Data API的持久性防御
the pencils friend and spring
铅笔的朋友和春天
intersection and it exports it's only
交集，它仅导出
package and it also opens that package
包，它也会打开那个包
and you see I did it a little
你看我做了一点
differently should have done it in the
不同的是应该在
other module as well but this time I
其他模块，但这次我
explicitly said okay I open it for deep
明确表示好，我将其深入
reflection only the spring core and only
仅反射Spring 芯，仅反射
to hibernate because these are the two I
冬眠，因为这是我的两个
know have to need to do deep reflection
知道必须做深刻的思考
on my classes and I allow them to but I
在我的课上，我允许他们但是
want no one else to be able to do that
不想别人能够做到这一点
okay so that leaves one more module the
好，这样就剩下一个模块了
rest API
休息API
and this is actually its smallest one so
这实际上是它最小的一个
it exposes one package and that requires
它暴露了一个包装，这需要
one more your internal module as a
再将您的内部模块作为一个
requires only spring work that's all and
只需要春季工作就可以了
it exports any one package so just
它可以导出任何一个包，所以
really easy so now except for one we
真的很容易，所以现在除了我们
migrated all our modules and the reason
迁移了我们所有的模块及其原因
why your module hasn't been migrated yet
为什么尚未迁移您的模块
because I defined it as a separate step
因为我将其定义为单独的步骤
because up until now
因为直到现在
I've actually been cheating a little bit
我实际上一直在作弊
because I'm compiling them as modules
因为我将它们编译为模块
defining them as modules but my main
将它们定义为模块，但是我的主要
application module is not a module yet
应用程序模块还不是模块
so I'm not running on the major part
所以我不是主要的
I'm just running on the class bar so I
我只是在班级栏上跑步，所以我
then don't get all the benefits from the
然后不要从中获得所有好处
module system but also I don't get all
模块系统，但我还不懂
the hurdles running it so last step is
运行它的障碍，所以最后一步是
add module descriptors in your major and
在您的专业中添加模块描述符
main reason why this is worth a separate
值得单独购买的主要原因
step because now you will run into
步骤，因为现在您会遇到
runtime issues so this will be a little
运行时问题，所以这会有点
bit of a memory right let's see
记忆的一点吧，让我们看看
okay there we go
好吧，我们去
sorry for this
非常遗憾
the last module descriptor
最后一个模块描述符
okay so this one depends oh sorry
好吧，这取决于你，对不起
oh yeah same issue always the same
哦，是的，同样的问题总是一样的
powerpoints overriding my sorry for that
PowerPoint对此表示遗憾
this matter okay
这件事好吗
you didn't miss a lot so it requires all
你没有错过很多，所以需要所有
my other modules in my application and
我的应用程序中的其他模块
then some spring dependencies and then
然后是一些Spring依赖项，然后
it exports to of its packages the one
它出口到其包装的一个
holding the main class and the other one
举行主要班级，另一个
holding a comforter spring configuration
保持床罩Spring 结构
class okay so now when I start it it
上课好，所以现在我开始上课
will run on a major part let's see if we
将主要运行让我们看看是否
get that working okay damn I forgot
让我忘了工作，该死的
something so it's now complaining about
所以现在它在抱怨
two more things that it are missing in
它缺少的另外两件事
the application module so Java
Java的应用程序模块
persistence is also needed here because
这里也需要持久性，因为
I use the configuration clause to inject
我使用配置子句注入
the entity manager so this is actually
实体经理，所以这实际上是
how I got to most of my module
我如何到达大部分模块
descriptor contents you get this error
描述符内容，您会收到此错误
and they say alt enter and IntelliJ
他们说alt enter和IntelliJ
helps you out she's okay there's
可以帮你，她还可以
something in your maven configuration
您的Maven配置中的某些内容
you might be able to use that okay so
您也许可以使用它，所以
add it to my module descriptor but for
将其添加到我的模块描述符中
the main one it's actually a little bit
最主要的一点
different for me because my other
对我来说不一样，因为我的另一个
modules use classes from the domain
模块使用域中的类
module in the public API so I can say
公共API中的模块，所以我可以说
okay you require them for my application
好吧，您需要我的申请
module but that wouldn't really be fair
模块，但那真的不公平
what's better in this case is and for
在这种情况下更好的是
this demo it doesn't really matter where
这个演示并不重要，在哪里
I define it okay this says it requires
我定义好了，这说需要
domain but it can also say requires
域，但也可以说要求
transitive saying okay if you depend on
传递性的说法，好的，如果您依赖
me you will also implicitly depend on
我，你也会隐含地依靠
the domain module and that's a fair
域模块，这很公平
choice because the class form that the
选择，因为该类的形式
main module are part of the public API
主模块是公共API的一部分
of this of this module
这个模块的
that should have resolved what issues
那应该解决了什么问题
let's see where we go now okay
让我们看看我们现在要去哪里
Auto one won't even start
汽车之一甚至无法启动
okay so modules okay again split package
好的，所以模块又可以了，再次拆分包
issue and this one is a little bigger so
问题，这是一个更大的，所以
I try to work around this by choosing
我尝试通过选择解决此问题
different libraries but then I bumped
不同的图书馆，但后来我撞了
into other issues until I realized that
进入其他问题，直到我意识到
this actually concerns only two classes
这实际上只涉及两个类
so there's a ajar on my class pop on my
所以我的班级流行音乐上有一个半开
module path with only two classes which
只有两个类的模块路径
both implement an interface from the
两者都实现了
other module and using Jackson so well I
其他模块，并很好地使用Jackson
can do that myself so that's a little
可以自己做，所以有点
bit more work so I prepared that
多做点工作，所以我准备了
okay so yes changes what that did here
好吧，是的，改变了这里所做的
in my security module added a new
在我的安全模块中添加了一个新的
package with two classes a little change
两类包装稍有变化
here in another class that's not too
在另一堂课中
interesting but also here in module info
有趣但也在模块信息中
you now see okay directly depend on
您现在可以看到直接取决于
Jackson what I otherwise would depend on
杰克逊我本来会依靠的
anyway indirectly so I've got that
无论如何间接地，所以我明白了
resolved and I see where are we heading
解决了，我知道我们要去哪里
next
下一个
ouch again okay this is in your face
哎哟，好吧，这是你的脸
illegal exes exception okay so it has
非法的exes异常好吧，所以它有
something to do with a reflection most
最与反思有关
likely I'm not opening up and again
可能我没有再开放
that's true
确实如此
okay so this is not easy I can actually
好吧，这实际上并不容易
more or less copy paste this to fix the
或多或少复制粘贴此以修复
issue
问题
so my application module let's see where
所以我的应用程序模块让我们看看
this doesn't open that one
这不会打开那个
can removed it and by now I already know
可以删除它，现在我已经知道
okay that gives me a hunch I might have
好吧，这可能会给我预感
forgotten another one here because it
在这里忘记了另一个
will also want to introspect the other
也会想反省
one okay so it's starting mmm
好的，现在开始了
short list again illegal exes exception
再次入围非法exes例外
okay yeah sorry
好的，对不起
this wasn't part of my plan but it's the
这不是我的计划的一部分，但这是
same issue but then in this current
同样的问题，但在当前
module so see
模块，请参阅
I hope I didn't forget one now
我希望我不要忘记一个
okay different kind of errors it's
好吧，不同类型的错误
always good that means you're out of the
永远都是好的，这意味着你不在
type of her you had before so there's a
你以前有过的她的类型，所以有一个
lot here okay
好多了
Oh class not found exception that's
哦，班上没有发现例外
interesting so apparently I also depend
有趣的是，显然我也依赖
on Java straw
在爪哇稻草上
okay let's add that as well so and now
好吧，让我们现在也添加它
the next one
下一个
again Claussen's fans okay bye buddy
再次，克劳森的粉丝们，再见，哥们
it's a bite manipulation library that's
这是一个叮咬操作库
being used by a lot of frameworks so
被很多框架使用
could have oh not the right one sorry
可以哦，不是正确的一个抱歉
shouldn't be here it should be let's see
不应该在这里，应该让我们看看
I'm not in my application oh it is
我不在我的应用程序中，哦，是
security sorry okay not really
安全对不起好吧不是真的
yeah sorry buddy
是的，对不起，哥们
and the cool thing I want to show and
还有我想展示的很酷的东西
here is IntelliJ helps you out here as
这是IntelliJ可以帮助您
well to find out where where it comes
很好地找出它在哪里
from so if I now click on this by
因此，如果我现在单击
biology actually is fully modular so I
生物学实际上是完全模块化的，所以我
go directly to the module description of
直接转到的模块描述
bye buddy oh it's really cool so I get
再见哥们，哦，这真的很酷，我明白了
more information there about de library
关于图书馆的更多信息
so starting okay looking better one more
所以开始好一点再好一点
now that's a strange one it's no such
现在那很奇怪，不是这样
method exception and there's some okay
方法异常，还可以
so CG lip is involved and this one
所以涉及到CG唇
really really took me quite some time to
真的花了我很多时间
resolve and required a lot of debugging
解决并需要大量调试
to find the actual root cause of the
找出造成的真正根本原因
issue and except errantly spring is
问题，除了错误地春天是
using some features of the jdk internals
使用jdk内部的一些功能
that you shouldn't really be using
你不应该真正使用
anymore but it's still possible if you
不再，但是如果你仍然有可能
then say Christ JDK has supported and I
然后说基督JDK支持了，我
really love the name of that module
真的很喜欢那个模块的名字
because it screams that you don't use me
因为你不使用我而尖叫
don't use me but it helps you out for
不要使用我，但是它可以帮助您
now although the name always already
现在，尽管这个名字已经
gives away a little bit of a guarantee
放弃一点保证
that towards the future you might want
未来可能会想要
resolve some issues but for now okay
解决了一些问题，但现在还可以
we're good let's see where we're heading
我们很好，让我们看看我们要去的地方
now okay actually started cool so let's
现在好了，实际上开始很酷，所以让我们
see if it works okay
看看是否行得通
first try to login it's working
首先尝试登录即可正常工作
cool next I want to create my board game
接下来，我想创建我的棋盘游戏
again because I wiped my database that's
再次因为我擦除了数据库
strange for 15 and supported media type
奇怪的15和支持的媒体类型
okay of course I saw this coming and I
好吧，我当然看到了
almost stopped acting now but and this
现在几乎停止表演了，但是这个
one really threw me off I had I think
我真的以为我把我甩了
eight hours of Investigation maybe even
甚至八个小时的调查
more in this before I find the answer
在找到答案之前，还有更多
and then I realized the answer was right
然后我意识到答案是正确的
in my face in the logs because if you
在我脸上的日志中，因为如果您
look here it says okay warning okay feel
看这里，它说还可以，警告还可以，感觉
to evaluate initialization bla bla bla
评估初始化bla bla bla
bla bla
bla bla
okay for the that all the way down okay
好的，一直下来
another deep reflection issue I forgot
我忘了另一个深思的问题
to open and the command package for my
打开和我的命令包
domain module that actually is being
实际正在使用的域模块
used as a type in my REST API so Jackson
在我的REST API中用作类型，所以Jackson
wants to do some deep reflection on that
想对此做一些深刻的思考
okay so this is the big difference
好吧，这是最大的不同
between where was in Step five
在第五步之间
just doing my modules one by one and
只是一个接一个地做我的模块
actually running on the module path
实际在模块路径上运行
so more copy/paste coding
所以更多的复制/粘贴编码
get rid of that get rid of that
摆脱那个
oh that sorry I hope your base that it
哦，对不起，我希望你的基地
to the wrong one
错了
it's of course my the main module that
这当然是我的主要模块
need to needs to open it hey there we go
需要打开它嘿我们走了
again
再次
okay starts or good I have to login and
好的开始还是好的，我必须登录并
now let's see if it works it works okay
现在让我们看看它是否有效
cool
凉
so can I also retrieve it I can retrieve
所以我也可以检索
it
它
hey last step can I get to bargain geek
嘿，我可以讨价还价了吗
ah one more issue okay something to do
嗯，还有一个问题好吗
with Jack B okay now I remember I
和杰克·B好吧，我记得我
remember I forgot one thing that I had
记得我忘记了我曾经做过的一件事
here initially so sorry board game geek
在这里最初很抱歉棋盘游戏极客
I changed the dependency in maven so I
我改变了Maven的依赖关系，所以我
now depend on the reference
现在取决于参考
implementation of Jax B and that
Jax B的实现
actually the 2.4 version is an actual
实际上2.4版本是实际的
module so I have to declare the module
模块，所以我必须声明该模块
name so final run fingers crossed
名字，所以最后的手指交叉了
so login works great me a board game
因此登录非常适合我的棋盘游戏
works now directly to the writings cool
现在可以直接将作品进行酷
if got it
如果知道了
we migrate it our application so it's
我们将其迁移到我们的应用程序中
now modular application um but for those
现在模块化的应用程序，但对于那些
of you who read my abstracts was a
读过我摘要的你们当中
little surprised it yet
有点惊讶呢
there's a bonus round I was also
我也有一个奖金回合
interested in Kotlin had this around at
对Kotlin感兴趣的地方
the same time so the first question that
同时，第一个问题是
came to my mind the Scotland support
我想到苏格兰的支持
modules and yes yes it does ever since
模块，是的，从那以后
version 1.3 of Kotlin their support for
Kotlin版本1.3支持
modules and the really cool thing is
模块，真正酷的是
they use the same module descriptor
他们使用相同的模块描述符
so the first it seems kind of odd do we
所以首先看起来我们有点奇怪
have a module
有一个模块
info Java in your continent project but
信息Java在您的大洲项目中，但是
in many cases like my case here it's
在很多情况下，例如我的情况
fine because you can have mixed language
很好，因为您可以使用多种语言
projects depending on the same module
项目取决于相同的模块
descriptor so there we go
描述符，所以我们去了
oh sorry let's close that
哦，对不起，我们关闭一下
so we're going into the main module and
所以我们要进入主模块
going to the most basic laws of my whole
遵循我最基本的法律
application the board game class and ask
申请棋盘游戏课并询问
IntelliJ to help me out here a little
IntelliJ帮我一点忙
bit okay more further down oh no oh no
好一点，再往下走哦，不，不，不
that's not what I meant
我不是这个意思
sorry wrong menu sorry okay come on
对不起，菜单错误，对不起，来吧
convert Java file to call in cool okay
转换Java文件以很酷的方式调用
so let's have a look there
所以让我们在那里看看
okay it's a little verbose over here so
好吧，这边有点冗长
we can get rid off this all so that's
我们可以摆脱这一切，所以
nice clean up then get rid of the
很好清理然后摆脱
imports okay so I've got myself a Kotlin
进口还可以，所以我有自己的Kotlin
class and okay got they're not
上课，好吧，他们不是
configured
已配置
oh please help me out yeah Java with
哦，请帮我
maven yes the main module okay go ahead
Maven是的，主模块还可以
so IntelliJ now sets some stuff up
所以IntelliJ现在设置了一些东西
including some maven configuration which
包括一些Maven配置
I know it's partially a wrong so I'll
我知道这是部分错误，所以我会
replace that this is the main
取代这是主要的
configuration that you require for a
您需要的配置
mixed language setup
混合语言设置
so the other thing I want to show is and
所以我想展示的另一件事是
it here requires Scotland that's telling
它在这里需要苏格兰
it and like I said my the main module
就像我说的我的主要模块
shouldn't depend on anything so this
不应该依赖任何东西
might feel a little bit you but where
可能会感觉到你，但是在哪里
you could think about it this is
你可以考虑一下
actually the same as depending on Java
实际上与依赖Java相同
base and every module implicitly depends
基础，每个模块都隐含地依赖
on chocolate base only difference here
在巧克力基础上唯一的区别是
it's explicit okay let's see
很明显，好吧，让我们看看
if I kept my promise
如果我信守诺言
okay completion takes a little longer
好吧，完成需要更长的时间
now especially because it's the first
现在尤其是因为这是第一个
run compiling my Kotlin but it's
运行编译我的Kotlin，但是
starting and well here I won't hit my
开始，在这里我不会打我的
colon class yet but here I will and to
结肠课还没有，但是在这里我会并且
prove that the whole application still
证明整个应用程序仍然
works okay cool so we've got that
工作很好，很酷，所以我们知道了
working as well so if you want to use
工作也很好，所以如果你想使用
modules and call it together doesn't
模块并一起调用不会
work so near the end of my talk so let's
工作到我的演讲快结束了，所以让我们
wrap up a little bit if you want to
如果你想包一点
migrate and I'm not saying that you
迁移，我不是说你
shoot this dog is definitely not about
射这只狗绝对不是
shooting migrate or not it's more about
拍摄是否迁移更多
how to do it if you want to do it go but
如果想做的话该怎么办
Irma so start with the very lowest
Irma所以从最低的开始
module in your dependency graph because
模块在您的依赖图中
that's the easiest point start has the
那是最简单的开始
least amount of dependencies get you
最少的依赖关系使您
going and that way you you can go
走，那样你就可以走
iteratively
反复地
over over your application but also
在您的应用程序之外
that's all your parts on every step
这是您每一步的全部
especially from the moment that you're
特别是从你那一刻起
actually running from the motor path
实际从电机路径运行
because you will run into runtime issues
因为您会遇到运行时问题
that you didn't expect and if you don't
你没想到的，如果你没有
test all your path before deploying to
在部署到之前测试所有路径
production then of course your customer
然后生产当然是您的客户
will run into these issues and for the
将会遇到这些问题，对于
more deluxe they have the answer so
更豪华的他们有答案，所以
that's the reason I kept the 415 and
这就是我保留415和
support media type example in is to show
支持中的媒体类型示例是为了显示
you that the libraries or the fragrances
你那个图书馆或香水
depending on might actually throw you
取决于可能实际上把你扔
off with wrong error messages whereas
错误的错误信息，而
the JVM gives really good output when it
JVM发出非常好的输出
comes to issues with the module system
出现模块系统问题
so always check your logs if your first
因此，请务必先检查您的日志
migrating to modules and you get
迁移到模块，您得到
unexpected errors it's most likely
意外错误很可能
module system had thrown me up and then
模块系统让我烦恼，然后
yet yeah too bad to say but it still
是的，不好意思，但还是
involves a pioneer so if you want to go
有一个先驱，所以如果你想去
there yeah you need to move it you need
是的，你需要移动它，你需要
to step up a little bit and work your
加强一点工作
way around issues that you might not
解决您可能不会遇到的问题
expect so with that it's a game over
期望如此，这是一场比赛
thanks for attending if you want to see
感谢您参加，如果你想看看
the code of my demo it's right there on
我的演示代码就在上面
get up if you want to contact me see me
起床，如果你想与我联系见我
on Twitter send me an email but more
在Twitter上给我发送电子邮件，但更多
preferably come to me have a chat ask
最好来找我聊天
some questions and also please leave
一些问题，也请离开
your feedback positive feedback but also
您的反馈积极反馈
definitely not negative feedback so that
绝对不是负面的反馈，这样
I can improve for the next run thank you
我可以改善下一次的运行谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]